

Summary

Passionate and well-qualified mobile developer with more than 3 years of experience. Working with Android and Flutter. Studying Agile, Clean Architecture, TDD, Design Patterns and Refactoring. I'm committed to the best way to produce high-quality softwares.

Favorite technologies



Employment history

Android developer at americanas s.a. October 2021 - Present

Flutter developer at Megaleios June 2021 - August 2021

Flutter developer at Bean Softwares March 2021 - June 2021

Jr. Fullstack developer at Thalamus Digital July 2020 - June 2021

Jr. Flutter developer at MFIT Personal January 2020 - May 2020

Education

Computer Science at Univali February 2020 - Present

English at KNN Idiomas September 2020 - Present

Projects

iCut

April 2021 - Present
Online barbershop marketplace.

Details

Itajaí, SC, Brazil contact@lucasbatista.me

Links

LinkedIn GitHub Blog

Skills

Refactoring
Clean Architecture
SOLID
Agile
Design Patterns
DevOps
UML

Languages

English

Hobbies

Hackathons, pair programming, teaching, code kata and reading.